Escape to the future.
Time Trap is a science fiction, adventure film directed by Mark Dennis.
A group of students become trapped inside a mysterious cave where they
discover time passes differently underground than on the surface.
Hopper, played by Andrew Wilson.
Cara, played by Cassidy Gifford.
Jackie, played by Brianne Howey.
Taylor, played by Reiley McClendon.
Veeves, played by Olivia Draguicevich.
Furby, played by Max Wright.
Time Trap is a 2017 science fiction action adventure film,
directed by Ben Foster and Mark Dennis.
Starring Brianne Howey, Cassidy Gifford, Olivia Draguicevich, Reiley McClendon, and Andrew Wilson, it tells the
story of a group of students in a remote area of Texas searching for their missing professor.
They then discover a mysterious cave by accident.
While exploring the cave, the group experience a series of bizarre and
dangerous events related to time and space distortion.
The film explores themes of time warp, professor,
cave, investigation, time travel.
The tone is thought_provoking.